International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Records on Microfilm 5432 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 1956: Reel no.6 (Reel 269)
  - Locals - Bellington, 1956; 3 (Reel 269)
  - Locals -Cincinnati, 1956; 4 (Reel 269)
  - Locals-Dalhousie, 1956; 5 (Reel 269)
- 1956: Reel no.7 (Reel 270)
  - Locals - Dallas, 1956; 1 (Reel 270)
  - Locals - Fitzdale, 1956; 2 (Reel 270)
  - Locals-Boston, 1956; 3 (Reel 270)
  - Locals - Kaukauna, 1956; 4 (Reel 270)
  - Locals - Longview, 1956; 5 (Reel 270)
- 1956: Reel no.8 (Reel 271)
  - Locals - Los Angeles, 1956; 1 (Reel 271)
  - Locals - Minneapolis, 1956; 2 (Reel 271)
  - Locals-Ocean Falls, 1956; 3 (Reel 271)
  - Locals-Pine Bluff, 1956; 4 (Reel 271)
  - Locals-Printing & Crafts, 1956; 5 (Reel 271)
- 1956: Reel no.9 (Reel 272)
  - Locals-Printing & Paper Crafts, 1956; 1 (Reel 272)
  - Locals- St. Mary's, 1956; 2 (Reel 272)
  - Locals-Tile Boards, 1956; 3 (Reel 272)
  - Locals-Vernon, 1956; 4 (Reel 272)
  - Locals- Green, Wm., 1956; 5 (Reel 272)
- 1956: Reel no.10 (Reel 273)
  - Locals-Willsboro, 1956; 1 (Reel 273)
  - Unions-Brown, A. E., 1956; 2 (Reel 273)
  - Unions-Livingston, J., 1956; 3 (Reel 273)
  - Governments, 1956; 4 (Reel 273)
  - Misc. - Accountants, 1956; 5 (Reel 273)
- 1956: Reel no.11 (Reel 274)
  - Misc.-Attorneys, 1956; 1 (Reel 274)
  - Misc.-Convention Call, 1956; 2 (Reel 274)
  - Misc.-Convention Material, 1956; 3 (Reel 274)
  - Misc. - Sullivan, H., 1956; 4 (Reel 274)
- 1956: Reel no.12 (Reel 275)
  - Misc.-General, 1956; 1 (Reel 275)
  - Companies-Chesapeake Corp., 1956; 2 (Reel 275)
  - Companies-Int. Paper Co., 1956; 3 (Reel 275)
  - Companies - Weyerhaeuser Timber, 1956; 4 (Reel 275)
  - Company Associations, 1956; 5 (Reel 275)
- 1957: Reel no.1 (Reel 276)
  - President Secretary Files, 1957; 1 (Reel 276)
  - Officers - Leavitt, R., 1957; 2 (Reel 276)
  - Officers-Oliver, L., 1957; 3 (Reel 276)
  - Officers-Sherman, J., 1957; 4 (Reel 276)
  - Officers-Sherman, J., 1957; 5 (Reel 276)
- 1957: Reel no.2 (Reel 277)
  - Officers-Sherman, J, cont., 1957; 1 (Reel 277)
  - Officers-Tonelli, J., 1957; 2 (Reel 277)
  - Organizers-Bergen, W., 1957; 3 (Reel 277)
  - Organizers-Cook, G., 1957; 4 (Reel 277)
  - Organizers- Derrickson, G., 1957; 5 (Reel 277)
- 1957: Reel no.3 (Reel 278)
  - Organizers-Datreville, Wm., 1957; 1 (Reel 278)
  - Organizers-Green, S., 1957; 2 (Reel 278)
  - Organizers-Hopkins, F., 1957; 3 (Reel 278)
  - Organizers-Kunstmann, I., 1957; 4 (Reel 278)
  - Organizers-Lauman, W., 1957; 5 (Reel 278)
- 1957: Reel no.4 (Reel 279)
  - Organizers-Leon, R., 1957; 1 (Reel 279)
  - Organizers - Petretti, J., 1957; 2 (Reel 279)
  - Organizers - Simone, J., 1957; 3 (Reel 279)
  - Organizers - Wade, R., 1957; 4 (Reel 279)
  - Organizers - Wentz, K., 1957; 5 (Reel 279)
- 1957: Reel no.5 (Reel 280)
  - Organizers-Wentz, K. cont., 1957; 1 (Reel 280)
  - Conference reports, 1957; 2 (Reel 280)
  - Organizers - Circular Letters, 1957; 3 (Reel 280)
  - Research & Education, 1957; 4 (Reel 280)
  - Research Dept. - Brooks, G., 1957; 5 (Reel 280)
- 1957: Reel no.6 (Reel 281)
  - Research Dept. - Brooks, G. cont., 1957; 1 (Reel 281)
  - Locals A-Z, 1957; 2 (Reel 281)
  - Locals-Aurora, 1957; 3 (Reel 281)
  - Locals-Cohoes, 1957; 4 (Reel 281)
  - Locals Edgewater, 1957; 5 (Reel 281)
- 1957: Reel no.7 (Reel 282)
  - Locals - Edmundston, 1957; 1 (Reel 282)
  - Locals - Georgetown, 1957; 2 (Reel 282)
  - Locals - Jacksonville, 1957; 3 (Reel 282)
  - Locals - Moss Point, 1957; 4 (Reel 282)
- 1957: Reel no.8 (Reel 283)
  - Local Unions-Moss Point, 1957; 1 (Reel 283)
  - Local Unions-Palmer, 1957; 2 (Reel 283)
  - Local Unions- Profile, 1957; 3 (Reel 283)
  - Local Unions - St. Regis, 1957; 4 (Reel 283)
  - Local Unions - Sturgeon Falls, 1957; 5 (Reel 283)
- 1957: Reel no.9 (Reel 284)
  - Local Unions-Syracuse, 1957; 1 (Reel 284)
  - Local Unions - Zallea, 1957; 2 (Reel 284)
  - International Unions, 1957; 3 (Reel 284)
  - Unions - Renick, B., 1957; 4 (Reel 284)
  - Unions AFL-CIO-Meany, G., 1957; 5 (Reel 284)
- 1957: Reel no.10 (Reel 285)
  - Unions AFL-CIO Meany, G. cont., 1957; 1 (Reel 285)
  - Federations, 1957; 2 (Reel 285)
  - General Files-A-Z, 1957; 3 (Reel 285)
  - General Files-General A-Z, 1957; 4 (Reel 285)
  - General Files-General A-Z, 1957; 5 (Reel 285)
- 1957: Reel no.11 (Reel 286)
  - Companies, 1957; 1 (Reel 286)
  - Company Associations, 1957; 2 (Reel 286)